ufcu.org 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy

## What does University Federal Credit Union do with your Personal Information?

#### Why?

Financial Institutions choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

#### What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and income
  * account balances and payment history
  * credit history and credit scores

When you are _no longer_ our customer, we discontinue sharing of your information as described in this notice.

#### How?

All financial institutions need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial institutions can share their customers' personal information; the reasons University Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

Reasons We can share Your personal information | Does the Credit Union Share? | Can You limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purposes—**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| YES | NO  
  
**For our marketing purposes—**  
to offer our products and services to you

| YES | YES  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| YES | NO  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes—** information about your transactions and experiences

| YES | NO  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes—**  
information about your creditworthiness

| YES | YES  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| YES | YES  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| YES | YES  
  
**To limit Our sharing**

  * Call Member Services at (512) 467-8080 or Toll-Free at (800) 252-8311 - our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) or
  * Visit us online: www.ufcu.org/privacy

**Please note:**  
If You are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we discontinue sharing of your information as described in this notice.

**Questions?**

Call Member Services at (512) 467-8080 or Toll-Free at (800) 252-8311 or go to www.ufcu.org/privacy

## Who we are

**Who is providing this notice?**

University Federal Credit Union

## What We do

**How does University Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?**

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

**How does University Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?**

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * open an account or deposit or withdraw money
  * pay your bills or apply for a loan
  * use your credit or debit card

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

**Why can't I limit all sharing?**

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.

**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.

## Definitions

**Affiliates**

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.

  * _Our affiliates include financial companies, such as UFCU Financial Services, LLC doing business as UFCU Insurance Services, a wholly-owned affiliate of University Federal Credit Union and UFCU Real Estate Services, LLC doing business as Member Home Advisor, a wholly-owned affiliate of University Federal Credit Union._

**Nonaffiliates**

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _Non-affiliates We share with can include insurance companies._

**Joint marketing**

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * _Our joint marketing partners include financial services companies (such as insurance agencies and organizations with whom we have agreements to jointly market financial products)._

## UFCU Privacy Policy Form

You may elect to stop all marketing from UFCU, its affiliated and nonaffiliated companies by completing this form. **If you have previously notified us of your election, no further action is required.**

Your UFCU account number(s):
